<resources>
    <string name="article_name">Zebrafish</string>
    <string name="Article">Zebrafish, named for their characteristic stripes, have been a popular test subject for researchers. Only
a few centimeters in length, the fish breed easily in captivity, grow quickly, and their transparent body
makes it easy to study their organs. Above all, they possess some amazing “self-healing” power. When part
of their heart is removed, they can grow it back in a matter of weeks. When blinded, they can quickly regain
the ability to see.
Recent studies show that humans and zebrafish have the same major organs and share 70 percent of
the genes. Moreover, 84 percent of human genes associated with disease find a counterpart in zebrafish.
Scientists thus hope that understanding the self-healing mystery of the fish may one day allow humans to
regenerate such organs as eyes, hearts, and spines.
Researchers at Vanderbilt University are particularly interested in zebrafish retina regeneration. They
have learned that damage of retina can cause blindness in zebrafish, yet it only takes about three to four
weeks before vision is restored. The structure and cell types of zebrafish retinas are almost identical to those
of humans. If the process can be replicated in humans, it may give rise to new treatments for blindness
caused by retinal damage.
In order to know exactly how zebrafish retina is regenerated, the team looked at the neurotransmitter
gamma-aminobutyric acid (GABA), a chemical messenger in the brain that reduces the activity of neurons.
They found that lowering GABA levels in zebrafish can trigger retina regeneration, while a high level of
GABA concentration will suppress the regeneration process. This suggested that GABA plays an important
role in the fish’s ability to regain their sight.
The team is beginning to test the GABA theory on mice. If that works, human trials will be next on
the agenda. If the research proves successful in humans, some of the nearly 40 million blind people
worldwide may one day have a tiny, striped fish to thank.
    </string>
    <string name="question_one">1. What can we learn about zebrafish from the passage?</string>
    <string name="question_two">2. Which of the following statements is true regarding GABA in zebrafish?</string>
    <string name="question_three">3. Which of the following is closest in meaning to “replicated” in the third paragraph?</string>
    <string name="question_four">4. According to the passage, which of the following is an opinion, but NOT a fact?</string>

    <string name="answer_one_A">(A) How they should be studied in labs.</string>
    <string name="answer_one_B">(B) Where they derive their regenerative ability.</string>
    <string name="answer_one_C">(C) Why they share humans’ genetic code.</string>
    <string name="answer_one_D">(D) What they may offer in medical advancements.</string>

    <string name="answer_two_A">(A) Increasing GABA level facilitates neuron activities.</string>
    <string name="answer_two_B">(B) There is a high level of GABA in the brain of zebrafish.</string>
    <string name="answer_two_C">(C) Lowering GABA levels in the brain can stimulate retina regrowth.</string>
    <string name="answer_two_D">(D) GABA contains chemical elements that trigger the growth of neurons.</string>

    <string name="answer_three_A">(A) Reproduced.</string>
    <string name="answer_three_B">(B) Reassembled.</string>
    <string name="answer_three_C">(C) Recycled.</string>
    <string name="answer_three_D">(D) Restored.</string>

    <string name="answer_four_A">(A) Humans and zebrafish have 70 percent of genes in common.</string>
    <string name="answer_four_B">(B) Zebrafish can quickly recover vision after damage to the retina.</string>
    <string name="answer_four_C">(C) Scientists are testing if the GABA theory works on mice as it does on zebrafish.</string>
    <string name="answer_four_D">(D) Understanding regeneration in zebrafish may allow humans to regrow their organs.</string>

    <string name="Button_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="Button_ok">OK!</string>
</resources>